crowdgather.com 2008-03-11

# Crowdgather - Find it on Forums

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.**

This Privacy Policy covers how Crowdgather Inc. (“Company”) will use its users’ personally identifiable information ("Personal Data") as well as general demographic information (“Demographic Data”) that Company gathers when users access and use this Site, when users use our Content or when users post their User Generated Content to the Site. Capitalized terms contained herein shall have the same meanings ascribed to them in the Site’s Terms and Conditions.

The Company knows that users care about how their personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you provide Personal Data to this Site, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of the Company and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.

(a) **Information Collected Through the Site** : We collect Personal Data through the Site when you voluntarily chose to provide us with such Personal Data, such as through one or more of the following options:

(1) **Registration**. Our Site's registration system requires users to give us your Personal Data, including contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address, phone number, and demographic information such as mailing address, sex, age, and potentially other personal information we may request. Such contact information is used to contact the user when necessary.

(2) **Forums, Blogs and Group Discussions**. Users may participate in forums and group discussions with other users. While we do not actively mine for your Personal Data disseminated in such blogs and forums, we will be storing the content as User Generated Content and therefore collect such information indirectly. We do not share your Personal Data with other users, we do not monitor the exchange of Personal Data that you disclose to such other users in forums, blogs and group discussions.

WE STRONGLY ADVISE AGAINST USING YOUR REAL NAME AS YOUR “USER NAME” ON OUR SITE, PARTICULARLY IF YOU ENGAGE IN FORUMS, GROUP OR BLOG DISCUSSIONS WITH ANYONE YOU DO NOT KNOW. WHILE WE ENCOURAGE THE FORUMS TO BE SELF-POLICING, SUCH POSTINGS WILL BE SEARCHABLE BY MAJOR SEARCH ENGINES AND THUS WE CANNOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR POTENTIALLY DAMAGING INFORMATION OR POSTINGS ASSOCIATED WITH YOUR TRUE IDENTITY. FURTHER, AS WE DO NOT SCREEN THE BACKGROUNDS OF OUR USERS, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE YOUR PERSONAL SAFETY OR PREDATORY CONDUCT BY OTHER USERS. THEREFORE, WE STRONGLY URGE YOU NOT TO SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA WITH ANY OTHER USER UNLESS YOU KNOW THEM PERSONALLY, AND WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY RESPONSIBILITY RELATED THERETO.

(b) **Advertisers**. We may display third party advertisements on the Site. In some instances, users may request more information from these third parties concerning their respective products and/or services by clicking on such advertisement. Some of our third party advertisers offer to contact our users directly as a way to follow up a user's interest in its products and/or services. In such cases, users will be asked for their Personal Data, and by providing your Personal Data in such a fashion, a user is consenting to being contacted by such third party.

(c) **Demographics Information**. Through the use of certain technologies we are able to track and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Site. The Company automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including IP addresses, cookie information, and the Site pages requested. The Company only uses this data in aggregate form, for statistical purposes, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users access parts of the Site so that we can improve the Site and the Content. This information may be shared with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregated basis, but it does not indicate the Personal Data of individual users. Our use of cookies and IP Addresses are set forth accordingly:

**(1)** Cookies are small bits of information that are stored on your computer hard drive by your web browser. Our cookies do not collect or contain Personal Data. While you may turn off your computer’s acceptance of cookies through your browser, your full use of the Site may be restricted.

**(2)** We collect your computer’s IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, report aggregate information to third parties and to conduct Site analysis. While we do not associate IP addresses with records containing Personal Data, we will use IP addresses to identify any user who refuses to comply with these Terms and Conditions or otherwise violates any applicable laws.

(d) **Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information** : We use the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Specifically, we will use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to provide the products and services offered on this Site, to maintain your account, to administer the Site and as may be otherwise permissible under applicable law. We will also use your Personal Data to offer you certain products and services you may find of interest. You may, however, opt out of receiving future solicitations by following the instructions in such email or by communicating your opt out preferences as set forth below.

If we intend on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

(e) **Our Disclosure of your Personal Data and Other Information** :

The Company considers your Personal Data to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

(1) **Business Transfers** : As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.

(2) **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties** : The Company retains the services of third party vendors to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ third parties to perform such functions, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

(3) **Advertisers** : We may share your Personal Data with our third party advertisers in order to contact you regarding such third party’s products and/or services. You may opt out of receiving these solicitations as provided in such solicitations or as otherwise stipulated under this Privacy Policy.

(f) **Legal Requirements** : The Company may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

(g) **Consent** : Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Data may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

(h) **External Links** : Our Site may provide links to various third party web sites which are provided solely for your convenience. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between the Site and that destination site, we do not exercise authority over these linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. We do not assume responsibility or liability for these independent methods or actions and are not responsible for the independent policies or procedures of destination sites. Similarly, we cannot take responsibility for the privacy initiatives or the content of such web sites. These links to third party web sites are provided only for your convenience, and as such, you access them at your own risk. However, we wish to ensure the integrity of the Site and its destination links, so any comments pertaining to the Site or any Sites accessed through these links are greatly appreciated.

(i) **Exclusions** : This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by the Company other than Personal Data collected through the Site. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any Unsolicited Information and User Generated Content you provide to the Company through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted or requested to be posted to any public areas of the Site. Except as otherwise provided in the Terms and Conditions, all Unsolicited Information and User Generated Content shall be deemed to be non-confidential and the Company shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information and User Generated Content to others without limitation or attribution.

(j) **Security** : We employ reasonable security measures in place to protect against the theft, misuse and alteration of the Personal Data under our control. Personal Data is stored in a secured database. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent or uploaded User Generated Content sent to or from this Site may not be secure. Therefore, you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us through an Internet connection.

(k) **Choice/Opt-Out:** Our Site gives users the opportunity to opt-out to receive communications from us and our third party advertisers at the point where we request information about the user. This Site also gives users the opportunity to stop receiving these communications at any time by editing their User account preferences. You will find an opt-out option at the bottom of all communications, or you may write to us at the below address to opt out of future communications not directly related to your access to the Site and your account:

Crowdgather Inc.

20300 Ventura Blvd. Suite 330

Woodland Hills, CA 91364

Attn: Compliance

(l) **Changes**. The Company may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, without obligation to provide notice to you. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used/collected. Since we may make changes in the way we use Personal Data, you are advised to review this Privacy Policy for changes each time you visit the Site. If we do provide you with notices to changes to this Privacy Policy, such notice shall not be construed as a continuing obligation to provide notice in any subsequent change to this Privacy Policy.
